{
    "id": "7e1b5b3f3a0a4820aa7be433c9de9a3f",
    "title": "Omission Of That",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sophia ………………… she was feeling better.",
            "description": "That can be left out after common reporting verbs like say, think and suggest.",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "said that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7b52995a151940ffa47c898b683c2e02"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………….. she was lying.",
            "description": "That can be left out after common reporting verbs like say, think and suggest.",
            "answers": [
                "thought",
                "thought that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b4ec24376d9441a8b15e6a7314bb6183"
        },
        {
            "question": "The doctor ………………………… I should take a holiday.",
            "description": "That can be left out after common reporting verbs like say, think and suggest.",
            "answers": [
                "suggested",
                "suggested that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "76442049fd9148869ca87ef406e3728c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… she was not coming.",
            "description": "That cannot be dropped after reply, telegraph or shout.",
            "answers": [
                "replied that",
                "replied",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "10b2641675e644e5963496614275ea3c"
        },
        {
            "question": "She …………………………. she was busy.",
            "description": "That cannot be dropped after shout.",
            "answers": [
                "shouted",
                "shouted that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "620d2b0178c04b89aa423584ace0edec"
        },
        {
            "question": "The judge paid no attention to the ……………………………. she was unhappy at home.",
            "description": "That cannot be dropped after nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "fact",
                "fact that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "04da36e5999447db83f0bd06879a2d61"
        },
        {
            "question": "She disagreed with my ………………………….. education should be free for all.",
            "description": "That cannot be dropped after a noun.",
            "answers": [
                "view",
                "view that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c03ed13bd1ce4b5b85eade0e4fa8c72e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Come in quietly ……………………….. the baby does not wake up.",
            "description": "That can be dropped after so that, such ….that.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "so that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7d73b33b26704896a9a4a5199c10fbc0"
        },
        {
            "question": "You can borrow my car …………………….. you bring it back tomorrow.",
            "description": "That can be dropped after provided. ",
            "answers": [
                "provided",
                "provided that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "79731999e38e4b40a9dcdeb29d3bb682"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is the woman ………………………. met in Mumbai.",
            "description": "When the relative pronoun is the object in a relative clause, it can be dropped out.",
            "answers": [
                "we",
                "that we",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "01cc29dcb02a480b946fc834029adb59"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is the house ………………………….. am thinking about buying.",
            "description": "When the relative pronoun is the object in a relative clause, it can be dropped out.",
            "answers": [
                "I",
                "that I",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0c6664c2af8b464a832492abb5b6b845"
        },
        {
            "question": "We were .................................... she won.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "surprised",
                "surprised that",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e0b076e930914baaa07f6aff9f3e79a8"
        }
    ]
}